<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PC on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/tags/pc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PC on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/tags/pc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Black Desert</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/black-desert/black-desert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/black-desert/black-desert/</guid>
      <description>Black Desert is a sandbox-oriented MMORPG featuring a dynamic combat system, stunning visuals, and a vast open-world to explore. With deep character customization and a variety of activities, it offers a rich and immersive gaming experience.&#xA;This Markdown content includes the game review for &amp;ldquo;Black Desert&amp;rdquo; with today&amp;rsquo;s date set as the default date (2024-04-23), the expiry date set to one year from today (2025-04-23), and the draft status set to false.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drawn: Trail of Shadows</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/drawn-trials-of-shadows/drawn-trials-of-shadows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/drawn-trials-of-shadows/drawn-trials-of-shadows/</guid>
      <description>Drawn: Trail of Shadows is a puzzle adventure game where players embark on a journey through a magical world filled with mysteries and challenges. With its hand-drawn art style and engaging story, it offers a captivating experience for players of all ages.&#xA;This Markdown content includes the game review for &amp;ldquo;Drawn: Trail of Shadows&amp;rdquo; with today&amp;rsquo;s date set as the default date (2024-04-23), the expiry date set to one year from today (2025-04-23), and the draft status set to false.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faraway 2: Jungle Escape</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/faraway-2--jungle-escape/faraway-2--jungle-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/faraway-2--jungle-escape/faraway-2--jungle-escape/</guid>
      <description>Faraway 2: Jungle Escape is a puzzle adventure game where players explore exotic landscapes and solve intricate puzzles to uncover the mysteries of the jungle. With stunning visuals and challenging gameplay, it offers an immersive experience for puzzle enthusiasts.&#xA;This Markdown content includes the game review for &amp;ldquo;Faraway 2: Jungle Escape&amp;rdquo; with today&amp;rsquo;s date set as the default date (2024-04-23), the expiry date set to one year from today (2025-04-23), and the draft status set to false.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghostrunner</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/ghostrunner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 14:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/ghostrunner/</guid>
      <description>Ghostrunner is a hardcore first-person perspective action game set in a cyberpunk world. Players take on the role of a cybernetic ninja known as the Ghostrunner, equipped with extraordinary abilities and a deadly katana, as they climb the Dharma Tower to confront its tyrannical ruler.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout 76</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/fallout-76/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 13:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/fallout-76/</guid>
      <description>Fallout 76 is an online action role-playing game developed by Bethesda Game Studios. Set in the post-apocalyptic wasteland of West Virginia, players emerge from Vault 76 to explore, build, and survive in a dynamic open world.&#xA;With a focus on multiplayer interactions, players can team up with friends or venture into the wilderness alone. Encounter other survivors, complete quests, and uncover the mysteries of the wasteland in this immersive Fallout experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/skyrim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/skyrim/</guid>
      <description>The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim is an open-world action role-playing game developed by Bethesda Game Studios. It offers a vast and immersive world filled with quests, exploration, and adventure.&#xA;In Skyrim, players take on the role of the Dragonborn, a prophesied hero destined to save the world from an ancient dragon god. With a rich lore, dynamic characters, and countless quests, players can forge their own path as they explore the rugged landscapes of Skyrim, battle fearsome creatures, and uncover hidden secrets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out Of Line</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/out-of-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/posts/out-of-line/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A unique adventure game filled with beautiful puzzles all hand-drawn in a unique 2D style . Out of Line follows the adventures of San in a quest to escape the Factory that was once home. Dive into a story set in a mysterious world that is revealed through multiple chapters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Get it now throguth [XXX XXX]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[LINK BUTTON TO EXTERNAL ADDRESS]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Never miss an offer. Newsletter, app, share link etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
