<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trello Learn on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trello Learn on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. Learn Trello board basics</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/01-learn-trello-board-basics/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/01-learn-trello-board-basics/index.html</guid>
      <description>Getting started with Trello is easy, in this chapter you will learn about the fundamental components of Trello, boards, lists, cards, and more.
Welcome to Trello! Trello is the visual work management tool that empowers teams to ideate, plan, manage, and celebrate their work together in a collaborative, productive, and organized way.
Whether you and your team are starting something new or trying to get more organized with your existing work, Trello adapts to any project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2. Create your first project</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/02-create-your-first-project/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/02-create-your-first-project/index.html</guid>
      <description>Trello is flexible and fast enough to manage any sized project from start to finish. Learn how to build your first board and start moving work forward.
Build your first project in Trello As with any project, you need to manage a lot of information, track task statuses, and pull in the right stakeholders at every phase of the project. The objective is to move forward at a steady pace and ensure you can deliver on time and within budget—all while keeping a smile on your face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3. Onboard your team to Trello</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/03-onboard-your-team-to-trello/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/03-onboard-your-team-to-trello/index.html</guid>
      <description>Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a team of ten or ten thousand, it only takes a few minutes to onboard your team members, set permissions, and start collaborating.
Information can easily get lost or misinterpreted when spread over many different tools such as emails or spreadsheets. Trello helps your team focus on the work that matters with its intuitive design, features, and integrations which minimize cumbersome learning curves and hours of tedious work. With Trello you can be sure everybody is on the same page to take projects to the finish line and has the tools they need to get their work done.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4. Integrate Trello with other apps</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/04-integrate-trello-with-other-apps/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/04-integrate-trello-with-other-apps/index.html</guid>
      <description>Turn Trello into your source of truth, break down communication silos, and connect Trello to all of the other tools your team relies on.
The saying is true—no one is an island. Working in silos is detrimental to your team, your business, and even your customers. Rather than working together to accomplish your common goals, silos put barriers in place and can lead to teams working against each other. Flexible tools and transparent communication help you overcome silo effects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5. Powerful collaboration features</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/05-powerful-collaboration-features/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/05-powerful-collaboration-features/index.html</guid>
      <description>This section goes over paid collaboration features available in Trello Standard, Trello Premium and Trello Enterprise. Read on to learn more about these features and click here if you would like to upgrade. Skip this chapter if you are not interested. Expand your work with two additional powerful collaboration features, advanced checklists and Custom Fields, available as paid features in Trello Standard, Trello Premium and Trello Enterprise. With advanced checklists and Custom Fields, bring more power to your team and learn how to scale your operations, add more power and customization to your workflows, and manage as many projects as you need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6. Activate different views</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/06-activate-different-views/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/06-activate-different-views/index.html</guid>
      <description>This section goes over Trello Views, a paid feature available in Trello Premium and Trello Enterprise. Read on to learn more about Views and click here if you would like to upgrade. Skip this chapter if you are not interested. View your work as a Timeline, Table, Calendar, and more &amp;mdash; toggle views instantly to bring clarity and perspective to your projects.
Like any situation in life, a project never looks the same from different angles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7. Automate anything in Trello</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/07-automate-anything-in-trello/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/07-automate-anything-in-trello/index.html</guid>
      <description> Trello’s built-in automation tool, Butler Automation, takes seconds to set up and can save hours of your team’s time. Learn how to build automations to tackle the tedious tasks that slow down productivity. SECTION OVERVIEW In this section you will learn:
Intro to automation Getting started with automation Rule based automation Card and board buttons Calendar and due date commands Automations for email and integrations </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8. Set permissions and admin controls</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/08-set-permissions-and-admin-controls/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/08-set-permissions-and-admin-controls/index.html</guid>
      <description>Scale safely and manage data securely without putting the brakes on collaboration and getting things done. Learn how to set permissions and administer teams successfully. Every team needs a digital space where they can easily connect ideas and projects across company silos. Allowing users to be added to a project based on their permission and accessing and creating content freely is key for keeping a healthy business environment.
By having all the control at your fingertips, your team can scale while keeping intellectual property safe within Trello.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9. Learn Trello’s top tips and tricks</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/index.html</guid>
      <description>Have fun while getting more done. Learn Trello’s tips and tricks, that will not only boost your productivity, but also add a little bit of delight to your team’s day. Trello embodies team spirit—the attitude, energy, and camaraderie needed for teams to accomplish great work together. We like to go the extra mile. Fun and customizable features humanize the work being done and allow the personality of the team to thrive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>