<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>9. Learn Trello’s top tips and tricks on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in 9. Learn Trello’s top tips and tricks on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Card covers</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/01-card-covers/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/01-card-covers/index.html</guid>
      <description>Card covers are a delightful yet powerful way of conveying information not only with words, but with color or images. Either as a header or as a full card cover, you can add an image or a color of your choosing to your card front. It will make your boards even more visual and help highlight specific information. We know it: you&amp;rsquo;ll judge the card by its cover.
With the Card Cover button, you can select if you want the cover to be above the card title or take the full height of the card, which will hide the card front.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Card separator</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/02-card-separator/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/02-card-separator/index.html</guid>
      <description>Break down your list of cards with a simple line break. Add 3 dashes (“&amp;mdash;”) as your card title, and a card separator is born! You can move the separator around between cards as your board evolves and changes.
Bring some humanity to the digital office An office, company, or any human endeavour are first and foremost created by humans. Humans thrive when they come together to build amazing projects. To make sure Trello places the human in the center of it all, we built some tiny yet fundamental and delightful features to make sure you bring your humanity to work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emoji reactions</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/03-emoji-reactions/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/03-emoji-reactions/index.html</guid>
      <description>Show your emotions at work and in context! Anyone leaving a comment on a Trello card can also reply with an emoji reaction. So when amazing things happen in Trello, don’t limit your celebration to just words—you can also get&amp;hellip; emojinal 😂
To add a reaction to a comment, just click the emoji icon beneath the comment and select an emoji. Or, click an emoji that has already been added to reinforce the feels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stickers</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/04-stickers/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/04-stickers/index.html</guid>
      <description>Add Trello stickers to your cards to give them some personality. Did you just launch a new feature? Add a boat or rocket sticker to the card front and let everyone celebrate your team achievement with a smile. For even more creativity, you can also pop GIPHY stickers onto cards! To access the GIPHY sticker set, go to “Show Menu” on the top right corner of your Trello board. Click “Stickers” and you’ll see the existing static Trello stickers (which in order to use, you can drag and drop to a card of your choice).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confetti celebration</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/05-confetti-celebration/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/05-confetti-celebration/index.html</guid>
      <description>Nothing is more satisfying than celebrating as a team. The feeling of work getting done and tasks crossing the finish line helps your team feel that all of their efforts have been worth it.
Exult under a rain of confetti when you drag a card to a specific list. Get in on the celebration train by simply placing any one of the following emoji into the title of the list of your choice:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark as done</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/06-mark-as-done/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/06-mark-as-done/index.html</guid>
      <description>When getting work done in Trello, make sure to share it with your team so that no one will have to interrupt your workday wondering the status of a task (and also to show how awesome you are, obviously).
Here are a couple of ways you can show off what’s getting done:
Create a “Done” list and move cards there when they are completed. It might make sense to create a new “Done” list of each week for standups and retrospectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/07-shortcuts/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/07-shortcuts/index.html</guid>
      <description>Trello has a ton of time saving keyboard shortcuts, which when added up should equal an extra coffee break a day or two. Within Trello, hit the question mark key on your keyboard to view them all, or check out this handy list. We can’t cover them all, but here are a few favorites:
Want to quickly view all of your cards on a board? Then Q is for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Additional Resources</title>
      <link>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/08-additional-resources/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abezaresdev.github.io/hugo/09-learn-trello-top-tips-and-tricks/08-additional-resources/index.html</guid>
      <description>RESOURCES BLOG: How to use Trello like a Pro
BLOG: Delight Your Day: 6 Remarkable Trello Features To Try
BLOG: Level Up: Pro Tips For You To Maximize Trello</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>